Assem Saber Abdel Hafez Mansour

Phone: +201111614288 Age:25

Address: Bani-Suif | Egypt E-mail: asemsaber98@gmail.com

Portfolio https://aseemsaber.github.io/My-portfolio_Aseem/ LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aseem-saber-gis

Objective:

An ITI Graduate specialized in Geographic Information Systems. With a strong background in GIS and its applications, I possess excellent skills in analyzing and managing geospatial data. I am proficient in utilizing various GIS tools and software, including ArcGIS and QGIS, and Envi, Erdas imagine, and I have practical knowledge of programming languages used in GIS application development."

Education:

Geoinformatics Specialization intensive Code Camp 3 Month (ICC) information Technology institute (ITI) Ministry of Communication and information Technology (MCIT) Minya Branch (Track team leader)

[Mar 2023 – Jun 2023]

(2021) Bachelor of Arts, Department of Geography, Department of Geographic Information Systems and Remote Sensing (GIS) Ba. With a Very Good grade (3.32) GPA and a graduation project with a grade of "excellence" with a full mark In A Study Flooding hazards, East of Beni-Suef, Using Geographic Information Systems And Remote Sensing (Project team leader)

[2016 - 2021]

Courses&Certifications:

- 1. Learn HTML &CSS- Organization(MaharaTech ITIMooca) (Issued Jan 2023)
- 2. Fundamentals of GIS- Organization (Coursera) (Issued March 2023)
- 3. STARTED WITH GIS-Organization (Esri)-(Issued March 2023)
- 4. Basics of GIS -Organization (Esri)-(Issued March 2023)
- 5. Spatial Analysis and Satellite Imagery in a GIS- Organization(Coursera) (Issued April 2023)
- 6. Introduction to GIS Mapping- Organization(Coursera) (Issued May 2023)
- 7. Geospatial Analysis Project- Organization(Coursera) t (Issued May 2023)
- 8. HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers- Organization(Coursera) (Issued May 2023)
- 9. Freelancing Basics Organization(MaharaTech ITIMooca) (Issued May 2023)
- 10.Getting started as a freelancer (Upwork)- Organization(MaharaTech ITIMooca) (Issued May 2023)

Work Experience

- Worked at SEDICO Pharmaceuticals in the production and manufacturing field from 2016 to 2019.
- Worked at Rameda Pharma in the production and manufacturing field from 2019 to 2020.

Technical Skills:

- Arc GIS Desktop
- Arc GIS PRO
- Arc GIS Extension
- Arc GIS Enterprise
- Arc GIS Online
- QGIS
- DBMS
- ERDAS Imagine

- Envi Software
- Remote sensing
- Image resolution Process
- PostGIS
- PostgreSQ
- GeoServer
- HTML5CSS3

- JavaScript
- JavaScript API
- Python
- ArcPyOOP
- Bootstrap

Soft Skills:

- Leadership
- communication skills
- Team Work Skills
- Self-Learning Skills
- Self-Motivating Skills
- Constant pursuit of growth and development

Language Skills:

- **English:** Very Good.
- **Arabic:** Native Mother Tongue.

Extracurricular Activities:

- Enactus Bani Suif University:
- [May2016 Aug 2018]

[2017 - 2018]

- Responsible for organizing events
- Responsible for the Sports Committee at the college as a Student Union member
- Attained second place at the governorate level in the 100-meter sprint race in Beni Suef [2015]